[
  {
    "question": "Which property we should use in HTML to open a page in a new tab?",
    "choice1": "_blank",
    "choice2": "_self",
    "choice3": "_top",
    "choice4": "_parent",
    "answer": 1
  }
  ,{
    "question": "To add a new row in the table in HTML we use:",
    "choice1": "<ht>",
    "choice2": "<true>",
    "choice3": "<tr></tr>",
    "choice4": "<go>",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "To break the line in HTML and display the content on a new line we use:",
    "choice1": "nextline",
    "choice2": "down",
    "choice3": "<break>",
    "choice4": "<br>",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question" : "The biggest header in HTML is:",
    "choice1" : "<h1>",
    "choice2" : "<h2>",
    "choice3" : "<h3>",
    "choice4" : "<h4>",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "to display a paragraph in HTML we use:",
    "choice1" : "<paragraph>",
    "choice2": "<pre>",
    "choice3": "<p>",
    "choice4": "<para>",
    "answer" : 3
  },
  {
    "question": "To add a comment in HTML we use:",
    "choice1": "<!-- comment here -->",
    "choice2": "<comment> comment here </comment>",
    "choice3": "// comment here",
    "choice4": "/* comment here */",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Tag in HTML is used to display the smallest header:",
    "choice1": "<h1>",
    "choice2": "<h2>",
    "choice3": "<h3>",
    "choice4": "<h6>",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which tag we use in HTML to show underline?",
    "choice1": "<under>",
    "choice2": "<i>",
    "choice3": "<u>",
    "choice4": "<_>",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "HTML is abreviation for:",
    "choice1": "High Technology Markup Language",
    "choice2": "HyperText Markup Language",
    "choice3": "Historical Text Machine Learning",
    "choice4": "How To Make Liquid",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "To add a title specificaly for a table in HTML we use:",
    "choice1": "<caption>",
    "choice2": "<h1>",
    "choice3": "<h2>",
    "choice4": "<h3>",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question" : "To display an image in HTML we use:",
    "choice1" : "<image>",
    "choice2" : "<photo>",
    "choice3" : "<img>",
    "choice4" : "<picture>",
    "answer" : 3
  },
  {
    "question": "To mark text with yellow background in HTML we use:",
    "choice1": "<mark>",
    "choice2" : "<marked>",
    "choice3": "<yellow>",
    "choice4" : "<important>",
    "answer" : 1
  },
  {
    "question": "To display code or a mathematical operation in HTML in the paragraph we use:",
    "choice1" : "<info>",
    "choice2" : "<code>",
    "choice3" : "<pre>",
    "choice4" : "<math>", 
    "answer" : 2
  },
  {
    "question" : "To display a horizontal line in HTML we use:",
    "choice1" : "<hr>",
    "choice2" : "<vr>",
    "choice3" : "<h>",
    "choice4" : "<line>",
    "answer" : 1
  },
  {
    "question" : "Which tag(s) we use in HTML to display text in bold?",
    "choice1" : "<b> and <bold>",
    "choice2" : "<b> and <strong>",
    "choice3" : "<b> and <bigger>",
    "choice4" : "<b> only",
    "answer": 2
  }
]